The way you crushed Mike at Ping-Pong was such a turn-on.
你用乒乓球打败迈克真的太帅了
You wanna...?
你想那个吗
You know, I'd love to, but I'm a little tired.
我是想  不过我有点累了
I'll put a pillowcase over my head.
我会用枕套把头包住的
You're on.
走起
- Hey. - What's up?
-嗨  -有事吗
Well, Mike's taking a shower,
迈克在冲凉
which,by the way, there's no law against.
顺便说一下  我们还没有做那个
And then we're gonna grab some food. So if you want--
我们想去吃点东西  所以如果你们也想...
- Finally. - Is that Ross?
-终于...  -那是罗斯吗
Yeah. You can hear everything through these stupid walls.
是啊  这烂墙不隔音
Sounds like he's with someone.
好象有人和他一起
He could be alone.
也可能就他自己
This morning I heard him do pushups
今天早上我听见他做俯卧撑
and then talk to his triceps.
后来还跟他的三头肌说话
Wait a minute, I think Phoebe's right.
等等  菲比是对的
Yeah, I hear someone else in there with him.
我也听见有人和他在一起
- Dr. Geller! - God, you're amazing.
-盖勒博士  -天呐  太不可思议了
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
都不用我说  你就这么叫了
Oh, my God, that's Charlie!
天呐  是查莉
She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
她背着乔伊和罗斯乱搞
Oh, that tart! Floozy! Giant!
那个尖酸刻薄的大只荡妇
I'm not sure about this.
这样做不对吧
Yeah, you're right.
是  你说得对
This is none of our business.
这根本不关我们的事
I'm not sure it's the best way  to hear everything.
我意思是这不是最好的偷听方法
Some one give me a glass!
给我个玻璃杯
No, I'm not gonna do this, okay?
不  我不会那么做的
I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
我不会偷听我朋友的
I love Barbados.
我爱巴巴多斯
I can't believe I'm kissing you.
我不敢相信我在吻你
I'm kissing Rachel!
我在吻瑞秋啊
I know. I'm her.
我知道  我就是她
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
瑞秋和乔伊  是瑞秋和乔伊
- What? - Get over here!
-什么  -过来这边
Oh, my God! I love how thin these walls are!
噢  天呐  墙薄点太好了
Thank you.
谢谢
《老友记》第十季第一集  乔伊和瑞秋接吻之后
《老友记》  第十季  第1集  乔伊和瑞秋接吻之后
Hey, before, you said that nothing could happen
之前你说我们是不可能的
between us. What changed?
为什么又改变主意了
Well, I only said that because of Ross.
之前这样说是因为罗斯
And then I saw him kissing Charlie.
可后来我看见他在吻查莉
What?
什么
Ross and Charlie?
罗斯和查莉
Wow! She's really making her way
她真的很想
through the group, huh?
加入到我们中来呢
- Eh, who am I to talk?  - Yeah.
-我干嘛干预人家这个  -是啊
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
真不敢相信  瑞秋和乔伊
How about the dinosaur twins
那边那对恐龙二人组
in the other room?
还没人管
- No one is manning that wall! - I'm on it!
-那堵墙没人负责啊  -我来
- Anything?  - I think I hear curtains closing.
-听到什么了  -他们好像把窗帘拉上了
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
我们这边已经把鞋子踢掉了
Bedsprings! Unmistakable!
弹簧床  不会错的
You realize that's your brother.
你有想过那是你哥吗
Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
你说出来才想到  来换我
Wow! Wait a minute.
等等
Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
罗斯和查莉  乔伊和瑞秋
Phoebe and Mike.
菲比和迈克
We're the only ones leaving with the person we came with!
我们是唯一没有换过人的一对呢
That's not true. I came with Monica,
我和莫妮卡一起来的
I'm leaving with Weird Al.
却要和古怪阿尔一起走
Okay, I've had it with the hair jokes.
好吧  我受够了这种头发的笑话了
Tomorrow I'm going to the salon.
明天早上我们走之前我会去发廊的
Okay, Buckwheat.
好的荞麦人
You gotta hear this,
你们该来听听这个
it's great! It's like free porn.
爽啊  简直就像是免费的A片
Is everything okay?
怎么啦
It's just-- I don't think I can do this.
只是...我觉得不能这么做
Oh, is it because of what might be on the bedspread?
是怕床单上有东西吗
I saw that report, with the infrared--
我也看过那些报道了  在红外线下...
No! No.
不  不
No.
不
Look, I need to talk to Joey.
我要跟乔伊谈谈
I mean, you guys just broke up.
你们才刚刚分手
Before anything more happens between us,
我们之间有进展前
I need to know he's okay with it.
我要确定他不反对
I completely understand.
我完全理解
All right, I'm gonna go find him.
好吧  我去找他
I just need a second before I can, you know....
我需要点时间  让我那个...
Grandma...
外婆...
- Okay, I'll see you later. - Okay!
-好了  过会儿见  -好的
That's the door. He's gone.
关门了  他走了
And she's turning on the TV...
她...打开了电视...
...and watching Miss Congeniality.
在看...《选美特工》
Honey? If you know it
亲爱的  如果你隔着墙
through a wall, you know it too well.
都能知道那是什么  那你也看太多了
Hey, what are you guys doing?
嘿  你们干什么呢
We're just-- We're sad to go,
我们...快要走了  都很伤心
so we're  just saying goodbye to the hotel.
所以在跟这旅馆告别
I love you
我爱你
Paradise Hotel Golf Resort and Spa.
天堂旅馆  高尔夫胜地还有水疗
Yeah. We had a great time, thank you.
对  我们玩得很开心  谢谢
Bye.
再见
Okay. Hey, have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
好吧  你们看见乔伊了吗
He's probably in his room
他应该在他房间里
with his current girlfriend, Charlie.
和他现任女友查莉在一起
That's the situation as we know it.
这是目前我们了解的情况
If you see him,
如果看到他
could you tell him I'm looking for him?
告诉他我在找他好吗
- You got it.  - Thanks.
-没问题  -谢了
Thank you.
谢谢你
Other wall, people! Other wall!
另一边墙  同志们  另一边
Rach, you there?
瑞秋  在吗
Oh, my God, that's Ross!
天呐  是罗斯啊
What are we gonna do?
怎么办
Okay, just be calm.
噢  保...持冷静
For all he knows, we're just hanging out.
让他感觉  我们只是在聊天
All right? So just be nonchalant.
好吗   随意一点
That's not nonchalant!
这不叫随意
No idea what it means.
我都不知道你说的啥意思
Okay, just hide.
好吧  躲起来
- Rach?  - Coming! Try under the bed.
-瑞秋  -来了  试试床下行不行
There's no room under the bed
床底下没空间
- Is everything okay?  - Yeah.
-没事吧  -没事
- Hey. Do you know where Joey is?  - Hi.
-嘿  你知道乔伊在那儿吗  - 嗨...
I really don't.
我真的不知道
Can I talk to you for a minute?
我能和你谈谈吗
Yeah. Sure.
当然  可以
I don't believe this. Have you guys been--?
我简直不敢相信  你们一直...
This is the listening side of the wall.
墙这边  只能听不许说话
Then she told me
然后她告诉我
that she and Joey had broken up
她和乔伊已经分手了
and part of the reason was she had feelings for me.
某程度上是因为她喜欢我
Right. Yeah.
是吧  好
You know I've wanted to ask Charlie out
你知道我碰到查莉的那天
since the day I met her.
就想跟她约会
Oh, I know, I know.
噢  我明白...
That's been really hard for you.
我知道你这些天来很难过
Anyway, one thing led to another, and...
总之  事情一件接一件
...before you know it, we were kissing.
还没反应过来  我们已经在接吻了
How angry do you think Joey's gonna be?
你觉得乔伊会多生气
That is hard to say, Ross.
这很难说  罗斯
That is hard to say.
这很难说
I gotta find him.
我要去找他了
He's gotta be here someplace.
他一定就在这什么地方
You would think.
就是啊
Joey?
乔伊
- Is he gone?  - How are you doing this?
-他走了吗  -你怎么做到的
What? Hey!
怎么  你们
What are you--? What is this?
你们怎么...  这是怎么回事
Have you been listening this entire time?
你们一直在偷听吗
Yeah!
对
Now, what is this?
那  这又是怎么回事
What is this? Well, let's see.
这是怎么回事  这么说吧
We kissed for 10 minutes...
我们吻了十分钟
...and now we're talking to our friends about it,
然后和朋友说这件事
so I guess this is sixth grade.
只有六年级学生才这样
No, no. Have you thought about
不  你们想过这会使
how complicated this could get?
事情变得多复杂吗
What about Ross?
罗斯怎么办
Look, he's with Charlie now.
可他现在跟查莉在一起
Yeah, but he wants to talk to you
对  可他想在正式开始之前
before anything really happens with her.
先和你说一下
And as his friend,
作为朋友
I mean, don't you think
你们不觉得
he deserves the same from you?
你们也应该这么做吗
You're a pain in my ass, Geller.
你太讨厌了  姓盖勒的
All right, you guys.
好吧  各位
Look, we appreciate all the advice...
很感谢你们的意见
...but this is between Joey and me.
但这是我和乔伊之间的事
And I think We can handle it.
我们能处理
We'll go.
我们可以回去
Will you do one thing for us,
可你能为我们这些
the people that care about you?
在乎你的朋友做件事吗
- Sure.  - Enunciate.
-当然  -去说清楚
Get out!
出去
Are they right?
他们说得对吗
Probably, yeah. I mean, maybe we should
可能吧  是  我是说
hold off until we talk to Ross.
我们应该先和罗斯说清楚
Yeah. Yeah. We can wait.
对  我们可以等
We don't have to do anything tonight.
我们可以今天晚上什么事都不做
Yeah, I think that would be best.
对  我想这样最好
So, I'm gonna-- I'm gonna take off.
那我要...我要走了
- Although--  - I like "although."
-虽然...  -我喜欢"虽然"
I mean, you know....
我是说
Ross and I haven't dated in, like...
我和罗斯已经有将近
...six years.
六年没约会了
Six years?
六年
Wow. That's almost as long as high school.
哇...跟读高中一样久了
Plus, you know, he is with Charlie now.
而且  他现在跟查莉在一起
Absolutely.
就是啊
- He's not thinking about you.  - No.
-他想的不是你  -是啊
I'm thinking about you.
我想的才是你
Yeah.
对
- Let's forget about Ross.  - It's forgotten.
-我们忘了罗斯吧  -已经忘了
- What's wrong?  - Nothing.
-怎么了  -没事
Seriously, what is it?
说真的  怎么了
Nothing. It's really...
没事  真的...
it's nothing. Come here...
没事  再来...
What's wrong?
怎么了
Sorry, I just...
对不起  我只是...
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
看起来我无法忽略罗斯
Well, maybe I can help.
好吧  让我来帮你
Your lips are so soft. Do that again.
你的唇真软  再来一次
Yeah, we need to talk to Ross. Yeah.
你说得对  我们真的要先跟罗斯谈谈
Hey. You guys ready to go?
嗨  你们准备好要走了吗
Not quite. Monica's at the salon,
还没  莫妮卡还在发廊
and I'm just finishing packing.
而我还没收拾好
Dude, you're not taking your Bible?
伙计  你不打算带上圣经吗
You're not supposed to take that.
你不应该拿这个走的
Besides, it's a New Testament.
而且这是新约
What are you gonna do with it?
你要它干什么
Learn about Jesus.
了解耶稣
- Hey!  - So did you talk to Joey?
-嗨  -你跟乔伊说过了
No. I couldn't find him.
没  我找不到他
I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
我会在飞机上跟他说
Okay. Sounds like a good idea, Dr. Geller.
好吧  好主意  盖勒博士
Stop it.
少来了
Ph.D.
大..."勃"...士...
You're filthy.
你真淫荡
Hey. Have you guys seen Monica?
嘿  你们见过莫妮卡了吗
Actually, I think she went to the salon.
她去发廊了吧
Oh, yeah. Oh, she went to the salon, all right.
对  她确实去了发廊
Check it out!
看看
Whose day just got better?
给某人的生活添姿添彩啊
Chandler!
钱德勒
Hey!
嘿
- What do you think?  - I think...
-你觉得怎么样  -我想...
I think I can see your scalp.
我想我能看见你的头皮
Don't you just love it?
很喜欢吧
Yeah. Yeah, you got shellfish in your head.
对...  你把贝壳挂在头上
It's something. You go, girlfriend.
了不起  向上吧  少年
- You never said that in your life. - Not once.
-你以前没这么说过  对吧  -一次没有
I thought so.
我想也是
Oh, and listen to this.
噢  听着
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes
没想到  这不光是视觉的享受
and the ears.
也是听觉的
Wow, it's kind of weird that
我和查莉分手后
I'm sitting next to Charlie after we broke up.
还要坐在她旁边  太奇怪了
Yeah. It's almost as if Air Barbados
就是说  巴巴多斯航空
doesn't care about your social life.
真是不关心你的私生活
Does someone mind switching
有人想替我
and sitting with Charlie?
跟查莉坐吗
Oh, I mean, l-- Dude,
伙计...
I spent the whole conference with Charlie.
我跟查莉整个会议都在一起了
- I understand.  - No, I'll do it.
- 我了解  - 不  我要的
Wish I could switch.
我要能跟谁换换就好了
I really don't want to
我真的不想
sit with Allen lverson over there.
跟阿伦·艾佛森坐在那儿
Once we're in the air
飞机起飞
and the captain turns off the seat belt sign
机长关闭系好安全带的标志后
...you feel free to roam about my cabin.
你就可以自由的在我的"机舱"里遨游了
And you should be careful
你检查行李箱的时候
when checking your overhead bins.
要小心
Because items may shift during--
很容易和别人的搞混的...
Oh, you're not good at this.
这个你不在行
You don't have to go home tonight, do you?
今晚你没必要非得回家  对吧
Yea, I think I can come over.
不  我想我可以来过夜的
It's Saturday, right?
今天星期六  不是吗
What?
怎么了
I can't do anything tonight.
今晚我不行
Why not?
为什么不行
I have a date.
我有约会
You have a...you have a date? With who?
你有个...你有个约会  跟谁
Oh, it's my girlfriend.
是...我女朋友
- You have...you have a girlfriend?  - Yeah.
-你有...你有女朋友  -对
Well, when you and I broke up,
之前我们分手后
I started seeing someone.
我开始跟其他人约会
- Well, for how long?  - Three months.
-那...多久了  -3个月
Three months?
3个月
Okay.
好吧
This is none of my business,
这可能不关我的事
but how long are you gonna keep seeing her?
但是你还想跟她好多久
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner.
今天晚饭的时候  我会告诉她结束了
I promise.
我保证
Oh, okay, good. You do that.
好  好吧  那你去吧
When you get home,
当你回到家
maybe there'll be a special delivery package
可能会有个特别的邮包
waiting for you.
在那儿等着你
Maybe I'll sign for it, tear it open.
我可能会签收  撕开它
Pull out the packing material--
扯开包装材料...
You know what. We'll have sex.
你知道吗  我们会做爱
Let's leave it there.
你不用再说了
All right, I'm gonna go talk to Joey.
我要去和乔伊谈了
I think this is the right time.
我想现在时机很好
He's in a good mood after the flight attendant says "duty-free."
空姐说完"免税"以后他总是情绪很好
Okay. Good luck.
好  祝你好运
Ross is coming over.
罗斯要过来了
I think now would be a good time to talk to him.
我想现在会是告诉他的好时机
I guess so. I'm just--I'm really nervous.
我想是的  只是...我好紧张啊
Well, keep in mind that by the time you're done...
好吧  你这样想  你说完以后
...they'll probably be serving dinner.
他们就上餐了
Still nervous?
还紧张吗
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
我要吃打卤面
- Hey, Rach?  - Yeah?
-嗨  瑞秋 -怎么
Do you mind if I sit here for a sec?
介意我在这儿坐一会吗
Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
不介意  当然不  不
Good luck.
祝你好运
- Hey.  - Hey.
-嗨  -嗨
So l...
我  呃...
I kind of need to talk to you about Charlie.
有点儿关于查莉的事要跟你说
Yeah?
怎么
Last night, after you guys broke up....
昨天晚上你们俩分手以后...
So sorry to hear about that, by the way.
当然我觉得很遗憾
Well, Charlie and I were talking, and...
查莉和我倾诉  然后...
You kissed.
你们接吻了
Wh-- What?
什...么
What? What would give you that idea?
你怎么会这样想的啊
- I saw you.  - Yeah, we kissed.
-我看见了  -对  我们是接吻了
But nothing else.
不过…什么都没发生
Nothing else happened, okay?
知道吗
- Ross...It's okay.  - What?
-罗斯...没关系的  -什么
It's okay. You know, look...
这没关系
...l totally understand, all right? You guys...
我完全理解  好吗  你们...
...make way more sense than her and I ever did, you know?
在一起比我跟她在一起更合适
And....
而且……
- I want you to be happy. - Are you serious?
-我希望你幸福  -真的
Yeah.
当然
- Now I have something--  - I am speechless.
-我也有点事想说...  -我真是无话可说了
I mean, the fact that you would
我是说  你居然把
put my happiness first like that, I mean....
我的幸福放在第一位
You're an incredible friend,
你真是个令人难以置信的好朋友
do you know that?
你知道吗
- Well, look, before you go--  - No, I mean it.
-呃...在你...  -不  我说真的
I mean, you're so loyal, man.
你既忠诚
And selfless and generous.
又无私  慷慨...
I am those things, yeah.
我是  当然是
I've known Chandler longer,
我认识钱德勒更久
so I think of him as my best friend. But now...
一直认为他我最好的朋友
...l may have to rethink some stuff.
不过现在  我得重新考虑一下了
Dude!
伙计
Hey, if there is ever anything I can do for you....
如果有任何事情我能帮忙的...
I can't think of anything.
暂时还想不到
- Thanks.  - Yeah.
-谢谢  -没什么
- So hi.  - Hi.
-嗨  -嗨
So you talked to Joey?
你和乔伊谈过了
Oh, yeah. We had a really good talk.
对  我们聊得很开心
- Oh, that's great.  - Yeah.
-噢  太棒了  -对
So everything's okay?
那一切都没问题吧
Oh, no, it's great.
没问题  简直太棒了
It's great. He's an amazing guy.
很棒  他真是好得让人吃惊
Oh, well, obviously, I think so too.
很显然  我也这么想
Well, I'm so excited about this.
对  我感到很兴奋
Really? Excited?
真的  兴奋
What, are you kidding?
你开玩笑吗
I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
我做梦都在想着要去干那事
Excuse me.
让开
You didn't tell him, did you?
你没说  是吗
I couldn't.
我没法说
He was saying all these really nice things about me.
他把我说得天花乱坠
I didn't want him to get mad
我不想惹火他
and take them back.
让他收回那些话
I'm gonna edge out Chandler!
我快要顶替钱德勒的位置了
Fine. Yon know what Joey. Forget it.
好吧  乔伊
When we go back to New York, I will tell him.
回纽约以后  我跟他说
Thank you. Yeah, I appreciate that.
谢谢  真的  我跟感激
- Hi, Mike's place.  - Hey, it's Mike.
-你好  迈克家  -我是迈克
- That was fast.  - Oh, no, she's not here yet.
-真快  -不是  她还没来
You know, I'm just gonna take off
我想我应该离开
and break up with her over the phone.
然后在电话上跟她说分手就好
You can't do that. Oh, come on,
你不能这样
Mike, strap on a pair.
这样太怂了  迈克
Why don't you tell her that we got back together.
怎么不直接告诉她我们又复合了
You know, women appreciate honesty.
女人欣赏诚实
We also appreciate gentle spanking
偶尔也喜欢
once in a while, just FYl.
被轻柔地打屁股
One more thing.
还有一件事
There might be a picture of Precious on my coffee table.
在我的咖啡台上有张宝宝的照片
Her name's Precious?
她叫宝宝
Is she a pure breed,
她是纯种的吗
or did you pick her up at the pound?
还是你在动物收容所捡来的
Any way, I just want to give you a heads up.
总之  我只想提醒你一下
Okay. And if she gets upset.
好  如果她不高兴了
...just scratch her tummy
记得挠挠她的肚子
and give her a liver snap.
逗她高兴
Hi. I'm Precious. Who are you?
嗨  我是宝宝  你是谁
- I'm Phoebe.  - Phoebe?
-我是菲比  -菲比
Mike's ex-girlfriend, Phoebe?
迈克的前女友菲比
The love of his life? That Phoebe?
他的一生挚爱  那个菲比
Oh, I can't wait for everyone at work to see these!
我真想让同事们快点看看这个
You go back to work tomorrow night?
明天晚上你才回去工作  是吗
Yeah.
对
So if you want people to see them...
那么如果你想让他们看
...you're not having them taken out, say, at the break of dawn?
也就是说你破晓前不会把他们解下啦
Well, if I had them taken out,
如果我解下来了
then I wouldn't be able to do this.
我就不能这么做了
You like that, right?
你很喜欢  对吧
What are you singing?
你唱什么呢
It's "Bolero" from 10.
《十全十美》里的波利乐舞曲
It's "Ride of the Valkyries" from Apocalypse Now.
那是《现代启示录》里的《狂热的瓦格纳》
Here's the thing. The cornrows were
是这样  梳辫子是
a solution to your frizzy-hair problem.
用来解决你头发的卷曲问题的
Now that we're home,
现在到家了
you don't have that problem.
没有那样的困扰了
If you think about it...
所以如果你考虑一下...
I hate them.
我讨厌他们
What? You said you liked them.
什么  你说过你喜欢的
Did l? Let's refresh.
我说过吗  我们回想一下
I believe what I said was
我想我的原话是
that I could see your scalp.
"我可以看见你的头皮"
Well, fine. So you don't like them.
好吧  虽然你不喜欢
Everybody else does.
可其他人都喜欢
Again, let's journey back.
再一次  让我们回到那次旅游
As I recall, Rachel said
我记得瑞秋说的是
she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
她以前从没注意过你的头骨的形状
And Joey?
还有乔伊...
Well, Joey didn't realize there was anything different.
乔伊当时看不出你有什么不一样
You know what? I don't care.
我不管  我喜欢这样
I like it like this, and I'm gonna keep it.
喜欢它  而且我要留着它
You're just jealous
你嫉妒是
because your hair can't do this.
因为你的头发不能这么做
- Get yourself in the tooth? - And the eye.
-敲在你的牙上了  -还有眼睛
Hi! There she is! Hi, Emma.
她来了  艾玛
Oh, my God, I missed you.
天呐  我想死你了
Oh, Emma, I missed you so much. Hi.
艾玛  我真是太想你了
Did you have a good time with Grandma Green? Huh?
你和外婆过得开心吗  呃
Did she give you a bottle of antidepressants again
她喋喋不休的时候
to use as a rattle?
给你抗抑郁药了吗
That was one time, Ross,
只有一次  罗斯
and they were only, like, five milligrams.
而且只有5毫克
Hey, Emma, Daddy has some presents for you, okay?
艾玛  爸爸有礼物带给你  知道吗
I want you to wait right here.
我想让你在这儿等一会儿
Come here, sweetie.
在这  宝贝儿
Ross, actually, there's something that
罗斯  我有点儿事
I really need to talk to you about.
要跟你说
Okay, shoot.
好的  说吧
- Okay. All right, here's the deal.  - Oh, no!
-好吧  好的  事情是这样的  -哦不
What is it?
怎么了
Oh, major shampoo explosion!
大瓶的洗发液破了
Look, Ross, this really isn't easy.
听着罗斯  这很难开口
Oh, it's all over everything!
还沾得到处都是
Why? Why me?
为什么  为什么偏偏是我
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
因为你拿了300瓶洗发液
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
对不起  对不起  你刚才说什么
Well, yeah. Look, it's about me and--
好吧...  是关于我和...
Oh, not another one!
噢  不要  又一瓶
Oh, my--Oh, and this is moisturizer!
天呐  是摩丝
It's even harder to clean!
这个更难清理
Why?
为什么
Why do bad things happen to good people?
为什么坏事总是落到好人的头上
Wow. Clearly this is not a good time.
好吧  很显然我来得不是时候
You think?
你觉得呢
Okay. Bye.
好的  再见
All right, so Mike's on his way over.
好了  迈克已经回来了
You thought you were meeting here,
你以为你们在这儿见
he thought at the restaurant, so....
他却以为在餐馆见面
It doesn't matter who's right or wrong.
谁对谁错不重要
The point is, I'm gonna take off.
重要的是我要走了
Wait. I'm not letting you leave
你告诉我到底发生了什么之前
until you tell me what's going on here.
我不会让你走的
I mean...
我是说
...are you guys getting back together or something?
你们和好了还是怎么的
All right.
好吧
Susie-- Can I call you Susie?
苏茜  我能叫你苏茜吗
My name is Precious.
我叫宝宝
I can't say that.
我可叫不出口
Susie, I'm gonna be straight with you.
苏茜  跟你直说了吧
Mike and I are back together.
迈克跟我确实和好了
And unfortunately...
并且不幸的是
...that effectively ends your relationship with him.
这样就要终结你们的关系
He's very sorry about that,
并且他对此感到很抱歉
and wishes you the best luck in all your endeavors.
并祝你好运
I just can't believe this. Why?
我无法相信  为什么
Well, I don't--
这个我也不知...
Why would he do this?
他为什么这么做
What's wrong with me?
我做错什么了
There's nothing wrong with you.
没有  你什么也没做错
What the hell am I supposed to do now?
那我现在到底该怎么办
Damn it, woman! Pull yourself together!
可恶  女人  振作起来
Have some pride, for the love of God!
看在上帝的份上  保持你的尊严
Okay, not a fan of the tough love.
好吧  你好象不喜欢苦涩的爱情
I just can't believe
我真不敢相信
that Mike didn't give me any warning.
迈克竟然没有给我一点暗示
He didn't know.
他之前也不知道
He wasn't planning on coming to Barbados
他也不是计划来巴巴多斯
and proposing to me.
向我求婚的
He proposed to you?
他向你求婚了
This is the worst birthday ever!
这真是史上最糟糕的生日了
Look, Precious...
听着  宝宝...
Mike's not worth this.
你不值得为迈克伤心
You're an attractive intelligent woman...
你是个迷人聪明的女孩
...and let's face it, Mike's kind of a wang.
面对现实吧  迈克太不是东西了
He proposed to me while he was still seeing you.
他向我求婚的同时还跟你在一起
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
他居然想在你生日的时候跟你分手
I don't like to kiss and tell,
我本来也不想炫耀
but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
不过这个周末他对你不忠的太多了
Oh, my God, you know, maybe you're right.
天呐  可能你说对了
Maybe I don't need him.
可能我并不需要他
I deserve to be treated with respect.
我应该受到尊重
Screw you, Mike.
去你的  迈克
You're a coward and a bastard,
你这个胆怯的杂种
and I hope you rot in hell!
我希望你烂死在地狱里
You're welcome.
不用谢我
Honey? You've been in there for a long time.
亲爱的  你在里面好久了
Is everything okay?
没事吧
Not really.
不
I have a problem.
我有点问题
Really? What happened?
是吗  怎么了
Well, I was dancing around and singing "No Woman, No Cry" ...
好吧  我唱着《女人不哭》跳舞...
...and I got stuck.
然后就挂住了
You can't move at all?
一点都动不了了
Oh, I can move.
噢  我可以动...
If I untangle you,
如果我解开你
will you please get rid of the cornrows?
你会解开这个稻穗头
I guess so.
好吧
Some of these look a little frayed.
有些看起来有磨痕了
Yeah, I tried to gnaw myself free.
对  我本来想咬开的
- Hey. - Hi.
-嗨  -嗨
- So? Did you tell Ross?  - Well, I tried...
-怎么样  你跟罗斯说了吗  -没有  我想说
...but then he had a shampoo-related emergency.
但他的洗发液出事故了
- So I guess now it's your turn again.  - No...
-所以我想该轮到你去了  -不...
I think it's better if you tell him.
最好是你去告诉他
You know, it's easier for a woman.
女人来说容易些
That way, you know, if he gets mad, all you have to do is go
你知道  如果他抓狂了  你就可以
I didn't mean it.
我不是有意的
I'm so sorry
我太抱歉了
Yeah, 'cause that's what we do.
对  女人是这样啊
Alright, alright, okay, uhm... How about this? Tomorrow...
好吧...这样怎么样  明天...
Tomorrow we'll both go
明天我们一起去
and we'll tell him together.
一起告诉他
Okay, that sounds fair.
好吧  听起来公平些
That just means, once again, we can't--
可这样我们又不能...
I know...
我知道...
That's okay.
不过没问题
I mean, we can control ourselves.
我们有自制力
We're not animals.
我们不是动物啊
- No! Of course, we can wait.  - Yeah.
-当然  我们可以等  -是啊
All right, so I guess that means good night then.
那么我想该说晚安了
Yep. Good night.
好的  晚安
Good night.
晚...安
Seriously, good night.
说真的  晚安
Stop saying good night.
别说晚安了
I'm so sorry.
真对不起啊...
Look what I found in the drawer.
看我在抽屉里找到了什么
And you said I'd never wear this.
你还说我永远不会戴它呢
Now that I untangled you,
我把你解救下来
how about you do a little something for me?
你还没报答我呢
Sure. What did you have in mind?
当然  你想让我怎么报答
I think you know.
你应该知道的啊
Really? I don't-- I don't really feel like it.
真的  但我有点不想啊
This is what I want to do.
我就是想要
Okay.
好吧
I just don't get why you like it so much.
我不知道你为什么这么喜欢它
She's a FBI agent,
她是个联调局特工
posing as a beauty contestant.
伪装去选美